nextjump.com 2007-12-05

# Welcome to NextJump

Privacy Policy (Last Updated on 8/10/2006)[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?companyName=Next%20Jump,%20Inc.&sealid=102&ctv_group=NextJump)

Your Privacy   
We are committed to protecting your privacy. At no time will we trade, sell, or distribute for free company specific or personal information, including email addresses or other user IDs, to any individual, company, vendor or organization, in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement. 

Next Jump Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site(s) www.nextjump.com, www.corporateperks.com and private label sub-domains delivered by Next Jump Inc., (i.e. uk.corporateperks.com , etc.). Because Next Jump Inc. wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact April Grey at corporateperks@nextjump.com, or by phone at (866) 639-8135. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php . TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

Next Jump Inc. complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union 

The Personal Information We Collect 

On Perks Sites   
Your first name, last name, valid work email address, and work zip code represent the only pieces of personal information you must submit to access the program. In certain instances, other demographic data will be collected, but not required. Perks uses this information to provide the benefits/services associated with the program. 

Additionally, Perks collects click-stream data and other preference information on its users in order to improve the design and vendor selection of the site. Click-stream data represents a page-by-page history of a person's site usage. 

Perks is a portal through which users access discounts redeemable at selected vendors. In most cases, online purchases facilitated by the the program portal are subject to the privacy policies of the Web Site where that transaction is conducted. In a few cases; however, Perks itself functions as the vendor and must collect additional personal information, described later in this privacy policy, to complete the online transaction. 

On Corporate Sites   
First name, last name, employer, number of employees, valid work email address and phone number are the only required pieces of information collected on www.nextjump.com and www.corporateperks.com. This is done on a voluntary basis and ensures that Next Jump Inc. can properly respond to all inquiries submitted through the site. 

Invite a Spouse/Family member   
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a spouse/family member about our site, we will ask you for your spouse/family member’s name and email address. We will automatically send your spouse/family member a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Next Jump Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your spouse/family member may contact Next Jump Inc. at corporateperks@nextjump.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

How We Use This Personal Information

On Perks Sites   
Next Jump Inc. requires your first name, last name, email address, and work zip code for the following reasons: 

1\. To provide a point of contact for communicating Perks correspondence, including your personal password, technical issues that may arise and periodic reminders that you may request (on an opt-in basis) as a Perks user.

2\. To assign a name to your user id and password.

3\. To verify your employment with the organization using Next Jump Inc. Perks program

4\. To provide the benefits/services associated with Perks 

Click-stream data can help determine the popularity of vendors, offers and site features with our audience, allowing us to develop a better site. An individual user's click-stream data is kept in the strictest confidence, and will never be distributed to any party outside of Next Jump Inc. 

On Corporate Sites   
Information submitted through www.nextjump.com and www.corporateperks.com is done so on a voluntary basis by individuals seeking to learn more about Next Jump Inc. Personal information is gathered to ensure a prompt and accurate reply by a Next Jump Inc. representative. 

What Information We Share   
Next Jump Inc. only shares aggregated data to third party vendors, but it will not disclose information specific to any user or company, including email address. This information represents a generic overview of our users' collective viewing habits and allows vendors to modify their discounts based on user traffic. Additionally, some participating corporations have requested monthly reports of traffic on the Perks program. These reports will reveal only the aggregated viewing habits of Perks visitors from that corporation. The reports will not disclose the user name, login ID or any other personal information of users, including email address.   
When users give money to nonprofits through out Charitable Giving program, we will share personal information including email address, with chosen nonprofit only if permited. Nonprofits use the contact information for acknowledgment purposes and to provide tax receipts. We will not share this information unless you **opt-in** and thereby indicate to us not notify the nonprofit of your gift. If you wish to discontinue receiving information from the respective nonprofit, please contact them directly.   
When users RSVP to an in-store retail event, limited information is provided to the participating merchant in the form of the guest list for admittance into the private event. This information is limited to your first name and last name, and if you will be bringing a guest. 

Cookies   
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Next Jump Inc. uses cookies on the site(s). Next Jump Inc. does link the information stored in cookies persoanlly identifiable infomation, including email address, you submit while on the site(s). 

Next Jump Inc. uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate the site(s). A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. 

Persistent cookies are set to store an encrypted link to your account information, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable Next Jump Inc. to track and target the interests of users to enhance the experience on the site(s). If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Some business partners (e.g., advertisers, tracking utilities) use cookies on the site(s). Next Jump Inc. has no access to or control over these cookies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.nextjump.com and www.corporateperks.com and private label subdomains delivered by Next Jump Inc. only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Emails   
Next Jump Inc. will not send unsolicited emails to registered users of Perks without consent. Additionally, users may choose to receive Perks correspondence, including email reminders of specific vendor offers and Perks newsletters. The "my account" channel on the site displays the correspondence you've elected to receive, and provides the option to unsubscribe from future Perks related emails. 

Opting Out   
All emails sent by Perks contain directions on how to unsubscribe from future correspondence. At any time, users may opt out of Perks related correspondence by sending an email to CorporatePerks@nextjump.com. Users may also access their personal information, including email address to make edits in the “My Account” section of the website. 

In addition, a registered user who wishes that their personal information, including email address to be completely removed from the Perks database should email CorporatePerks@nextjump.com. We will respond to your request within twenty [20] business days. An employee's complete removal of his or her personal information from the database negates that employee's ability to login to Perks 

Notification Of Changes To Privacy Policy   
Users will be notified of changes or revisions to this privacy policy, including our email practives, by a notice posted on the Perks login page. The notice will contain a link, whereby the Privacy policy can be examined in full. In this way registered users are made aware of policy changes prior to shopping or browsing the Web Site. As always, a user who is not amenable to the conditions of a revised privacy policy may opt out of Perks by means outlined earlier in this document. 

Purchasing Items Directly Through the Perks Site

Agents   
Next Jump Inc. uses an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain share, store or use personally identifiable information, including email address, for any other purposes. 

Service Providers   
Next Jump Inc. uses other third parties to process credit card transactions on the site(s). When you sign up for programs directly related to Perks, Next Jump Inc. will share first name, last name, credit card information and billing address as necessary for the third party to provide that service. No other information is shared with their parties for this purpose. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information, including email address, for any other purpose. 

Perks is a portal that provides access to exclusive discounts redeemable at the point of purchase at a certain vendor's online or offline location. In rare cases, Perks may serve as both vendor and portal, and will collect certain information necessary to complete an online purchase. Like every online purchase, you will be required to submit the following information to buy an item where Perks is the vendor: 

• Shipping or billing address or both  
• Credit card information  
• Day time phone number  
• Email address 

In all cases, any transaction conducted through Perks is secured and encrypted with SSL technology, and certified by Verisign. Hence, you may submit any sensitive data (e.g., credit card numbers) to this site with the assurance that it will remain protected. 

All email addresses are safeguarded through database encryption in both sitting and transmitting states. At no point are email address disclosed or shared for purposes not outlined in this statement. 

Again, Perks will never compromise your personal privacy. Information, including email address, submitted to carry out a transaction where Next Jump Inc. is the vendor is kept in the highest confidentiality, and is absolutely never shared with outside parties in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement. 

Vendor's Privacy   
Perks is a portal that enables users to purchase discounted products on the Web Sites of participating vendors. Each vendor maintains its' own privacy policy that you should be familiar with before you submit your personal information. Our privacy policy is not applicable on any of the vendor sites. Therefore, it is important for a potential buyer to familiarize himself with the privacy policies of each vendor. 

Next Jump, Inc will never transmit personal identifiers, including name, email address, or user ids to any participating vendor. Clicking on a vendor site through Perks does not result in the transmission of your personal information to that vendor. 

Limits   
Although your privacy is of paramount concern to us, Next Jump Inc. cannot reasonably be expected to suppress information where the withholding of such information represents a violation of federal or state law. 

Next Jump Inc. reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information, icluding email address, as required by law and when it is believed that disclosure is necessary to protect Next Jump Inc.’s rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the site(s). 

Your Consent   
As a user of Perks, you consent to our collection and storage of your personal information, including email address, (as defined above) in our database, and to our use of aggregated and non-personal information generated by the viewing habits of our users. 

In Summary:   
Next Jump Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. Next Jump Inc. does not sell, trade, give away, or rent personal or company information, including email address, to any outside parties in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement. 

Next Jump Inc. uses the information collected on the site to make shopping and promotional activities possible and to enhance your overall experience with Perks. 

Contact Us   
Please direct your questions or comments to: 

By Email: corporateperks@nextjump.com  
By Phone: (866) 639-8135 

By Mail:  
ATTN: Customer Service Department  
Next Jump Inc.   
261 Fifth Avenue, 8th Floor  
New York, NY 10016
